<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>seikaisha on Unikansou</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/seikaisha/</link>
    <description>Recent content in seikaisha on Unikansou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:36:42 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/seikaisha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yuurei Ressha to Konpeitou - 幽霊列車とこんぺい糖</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/seikaisha/rigaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/seikaisha/rigaya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/rigaya/rigaya1.jpg&#34; width=&#34;70%&#34;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: 幽霊列車とこんぺい糖 新装版 &lt;br/&gt;
Author: 木ノ歌 詠 &lt;br/&gt;
Label: 星海社FICTIONS&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s a republished book from the defunct Fujimi Mystery Bunko label, Seikaisha has made a really nice version with nice color illustration and great presentation (as usual from Seikaisha). A good thing because the old version was considering as some sort of yuri classic but the only way to obtain was to pay 6k yen plus in the secondhand market.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hatenaki Ten no Fatalsis - 果てなき天のファタルシス</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/seikaisha/fatalsis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/seikaisha/fatalsis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/fatalsis/1.jpg&#34; width=&#34;70%&#34;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: 果てなき天のファタルシス &lt;br/&gt;
Author: 十文字 青 &lt;br/&gt;
Label: 星海社FICTIONS&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Written by Ao Jyumonji originally released in the Doujin magazine Black Past in 2012, rerelased by Seikaisha in 2013 with illustrations by Nekomegane. This book is very reminiscent from the early 00s Otaku sphere like Last Resort, Iriya, Bokurano and company; Jyumonji wanted to write a book focused on war so it has a lot more action and military elements into the mix too.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Psyche</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/seikaisha/%E8%83%A1%E8%9D%B6%E3%81%AE%E5%A4%A2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jan 2022 00:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/books/seikaisha/%E8%83%A1%E8%9D%B6%E3%81%AE%E5%A4%A2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/psyche/1.jpg&#34; width=&#34;70%&#34;/&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: Psyche &lt;br/&gt;
Author: 唐辺 葉介 &lt;br/&gt;
Label: 星海社文庫&lt;/em&gt; &lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Debut novel of Setoguchi under the Karabe pen name. On his second year of highschool Nao is living alone in his family house after being the only survivor from a plane accident. He still can see all the members from his family hanging around the house as ghosts so he still lives his ordinary live going to school, practising his painting hobby, fighting his sister for the shower, etc. Everyone that has read some Setoguchi knows he has a very peculiar way of writing protagonists, they are more often than not somewhat lacking emotion, with a more analitical way of perceiving the world, they can’t connect with the rest of the world, almost reaching the point where it kind of “mocks” or critizes human stupidity in a nonchalantly way. Nao fits perfectly into that but let’s say he is not doing very well mentally.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
