<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>doujin on Unikansou</title>
    <link>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/tags/doujin/</link>
    <description>Recent content in doujin on Unikansou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:36:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/tags/doujin/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Haiyuuenchi no Memento Memoria - 廃遊園地のメメントメモリア</title>
      <link>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/memento_memoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2023 00:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/memento_memoria/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/images/memento_memoria/0.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: 廃遊園地のメメントメモリア&lt;br/&gt;
Developer: Asanoha Seisakujo&lt;br/&gt;
vndb: &lt;a href=&#34;https://vndb.org/v44700&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://vndb.org/v44700&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A new doujin VN released at C102, caught my attention looking up new releases since it looked fresh from a new circle with cool setting and nice art.
It&amp;rsquo;s in some sort of dystopian future where WW3 has been going on for years. The protagonist Kai is some soldier for Lagoon, a city made from and for kids completly aside of adults in an amusement park, looked like some Peter Pan city.
In a mission he meets with Mio a girl soldier who&amp;rsquo;s been abandoned and decides to help her out. He soon discovers that her brain memories works through a NM-card, a device similar to some sort of disk drive that stores her memories since she can&amp;rsquo;t do it naturally. Soon enough they start living together in Lagoon developing a relationship.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ihanashi no Majo - イハナシの魔女</title>
      <link>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/ihanashi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 00:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/ihanashi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/images/ihanashi/0.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: イハナシの魔女&lt;br/&gt;
Developer: Fragaria&lt;br/&gt;
vndb: &lt;a href=&#34;https://vndb.org/v32758&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://vndb.org/v32758&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This doujin VN has been moving some sort of waves since it was released last year at summer comiket, it&amp;rsquo;s been pretty popular around Japanese circle and it&amp;rsquo;s already officially translated to Chinese and Korean and I kinda expect an English TL soon too, wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be suprised. When Kemco announced their console port I got curious since they don&amp;rsquo;t really do ports of other games. I Grabbed it without knowing what to expect but to my surprise it was totally my kind of shit since it&amp;rsquo;s some ボーイミーツガール セカイ系ish with a lot of supernatural 伝奇 SF stuff.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plot follows Hikaru as the protagonist that until now his live has been some kind of hell with his parents dying when he was 5, been bullied in school and by his aunt too until one day she ditches him sending him to a small island in Okinawa with his grandfather who has been missing for god knows when. He finds himself homeless in the island and meets with a cold enigmatic girl called Lilun in similar circumstances, He tries to get closer to her to survive and soon enough he discovers she is a real witch that comes from a different world that can use magic. From there they start living together trying to discover the secrets of this magic and its link with the past of this island.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rakujitsu - 落日</title>
      <link>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/%E8%90%BD%E6%97%A5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 23:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/%E8%90%BD%E6%97%A5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/tBnOF2q1rsE&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: 落日 &lt;br/&gt;
Developer: ののの通信 &lt;br/&gt;
vndb: &lt;a href=&#34;https://vndb.org/v21105&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://vndb.org/v21105&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Short doujin VN focused around the struggles of facing the exams to enter university. The protagonist doesn&amp;rsquo;t have any dreams about what he wants to do with his life but since everyone says going to college and getting a job is the most likely way to achieve happiness in life, he&amp;rsquo;s determined to follow that path. Close to his house there&amp;rsquo;s a rooftop where he goes on Sundays at sunset (hence the game&amp;rsquo;s name), where he regularly meets two girls that seem the polar opposite of each other, Manami and Ren, both of them are also in his last year of school with the exams coming up soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ore-tachi ga Shinda Natsu, Tenshi no Ita Mikkakan - 俺たちが死んだ夏、天使のいた三日間</title>
      <link>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/oreten/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2019 20:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://uunniiblog.github.io/unikansou/posts/vns/oreten/</guid>
      <description>Title: 俺たちが死んだ夏、天使のいた三日間 Developer: Check&amp;amp;Stripe vndb: https://vndb.org/v13296 In my never ending search for more セカイ系 I found this short doujin game I quite liked. The story follows Kousuke, a guy that has gone through some tragic shit in his life which lead him into having a sad and negative attitude towards everything.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
