<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Waffle on Unikansou</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/waffle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Waffle on Unikansou</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:36:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/waffle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Imouto to Kanojo - 妹と彼女 それぞれの選択</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/vns/schizogaslightingimoutorenaiadv/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2024 00:36:42 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/vns/schizogaslightingimoutorenaiadv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;center&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/imokano/0.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Title: 妹と彼女 それぞれの選択&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;Developer: Waffle&lt;br/&gt;&#xA;vndb: &lt;a href=&#34;https://vndb.org/v31003&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://vndb.org/v31003&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/center&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I just finished Imouto to Kanojo, one of the most interesting romance drama VN I&amp;rsquo;ve read, Masaki Shunsuke&amp;rsquo;s writing is really something else; it&amp;rsquo;s very captivating and mood-setting. The way he structures and plots his routes is unlike anything else; hes great at playing with your expectations to the point that I&amp;rsquo;m sure wether you have played his earlier title Hajimete no Kanojo or not would also change your way of approaching Imokano&#xA;From what I&amp;rsquo;ve heard Hajimete no Kanojo started as some sort of nukige but the writer decided to take it to the next level when (I imagine) he realized he could do something interesting there; as a result it is kind of a glorified nukige since it has like a hundreds ero scenes but also it has a interesting display of his writing abilities playing some tricks between the protagonist and reader&amp;rsquo;s pov accompanied by some cool character writing, especially when you get to the &amp;ldquo;ura&amp;rdquo; routes and his unconventional way of &amp;ldquo;ending&amp;rdquo; the routes also hit me hard since it&amp;rsquo;s not something you usually see in eroge, they&amp;rsquo;re very FullDespair and play with your expectations building up between them.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
